Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel.
Friends, in today's video, we will
talk about ICC Prudential Life
Insurance Job and learn
how to apply for it and
who will apply, what education
qualification is required, whether you will get it here
or not, how to apply,
complete information will be
given to you in this section. Before moving forward,
if you have not subscribed to our channel, then please
subscribe and
also press the bell icon so that all the
banking and private jobs
information that comes in the future reaches you first.
How will you get it, friends, if you search ICC Prudential
Life Insurance Career or ICC
Prudential on YouTube, then
most of the videos will be
mine and here almost many
students have got the job from here, so I
just urge you to
apply for this job, you can also get the job from here,
you can get it here in two ways,
you can get it through advisory, the
second one is full time or permanent job,
you can also get this if  If you are 12th pass or a
little undergraduate or graduate, then
you will definitely get it from here,
friends, what I am telling you,
I have already told you in five videos before this
and many
students have benefited from there, when they have got it, you should
also apply, so you will definitely get it
from here, friends, if
you have heard the name here ICC
Prudential Life Insurance, then you are probably thinking that
you will have to do sales, you will definitely have to do
sales here,
but compare to Aadhar Company, which
is the largest in the market,
if you sell any product here, then
just by hearing the name of the company,
more than half of the customer's doubts get cleared, due to
which you will not have that much pressure here,
okay, so one
good idea, if you want to do it, then
I will tell you the details further, you can
get it in two ways, either you
can give a walking interview or else you
can apply online, I will
also give you
information about how to apply online, first of all education  Let's
talk about qualifications,
friends, if you have passed 12th, then you
can join as an advisor. The most you
can do is just hire your candidate,
record it, and train it in the
insurance product. So, in
a way,
you can generate income from here as well. But yes, in the
advisor's job, you don't get salary here; you get it
from commission.
And in the full-time permanent job, you
get salary in regular jobs. I am going to tell you how to apply for full-time permanent.
But first, let me tell you about the salary here,
friends. I have seen that compared to other
companies, you can get a
higher salary than that
in potential life insurance here.
Sometimes, friends,
even those who are in pressure, you can get a salary of Rs. 14, 15,000 or 16,000 here.
If you have two-three years of experience, then
what's the big deal in this?
You will get more information about salary and story here, the
answer to this is what is this profile, the
profile will be very good, what will your
profile be like, so let's go to
our computer screen, there
we will tell you step by step here on
our computer screen and from
here we will apply and tell you
friends, regarding if you
need information about story also, then you can also
visit our website which is dekho.net,
there also you will get banking job and
government job, private job, so
friends, let's talk to you here about how to
apply for this job, first of all here and I will
give you an example information as to
why you have to join here, friends, you have to join
because you can get maximum knowledge from here, you will get maximum
trading and support here, it
is one of the largest company and one of the good company in the market at today's
rate, apart from this, friends,
if you go to role here, then what role can you get
here, so I will tell you here,
as you can see here that from here
That is, the answer to the advisory is bank
insurance and direct marketing customer
service and operations and here
apart from that the story can be found only here, you will
go to NC like I
told you earlier that when you
can do bank insurance here, friends this will be a good
answer here, so
you have to sell the insurance product while sitting inside the bank,
in direct marketing you will get
leads from the company, you have to
follow up on them and generate revenue from there,
in customer service and operations
also you have to do this work only while sitting in the office,
you have to do business on behalf of all the walking customers who will come, all the rest
like human
resources, finance, these are different
departments, you can do it from here also to
apply, friends from here
you will simply go to home and
when you go here from the story,
set the location from here,
for which location you should do it here, so
I
am late, whatever location you have from my location, by
selecting the location here
you can apply here  You can search here as you
will search, all the items that come here will be
visible to you here, friends,
whatever items are there here, friends, I am
also providing you a good special sale here,
if I talk
friends, to pay here, then there is
an option here, so see, here is the Financial
Service Consultant of the bank, that is, the Financial Service
Consultant, it will
come to you under Bank Insurance, that is, this item,
friends, whether it is ICC Bank
or any bank, where you get the
posting done, you will have to go there and do business related to the
walking customers who will come from within the bank,
you will have to
generate the business from there, to play the application
simply, secondly, we will have to
click here and after that
friends, a page will open in front of you
where you will have to file all your details here,
first of all when it is locations, when it is
in location, like I
selected Hyderabad, then
Hyderabad will automatically be added here, after that
friends, first time, middle name, last time, if there is
no middle name, then
mention first and last time, give email ID and phone number  The
phone which you use, because the
call will come to you from the company from here,
you will have to pick up the date of birth,
after that you will have to select the gender here and then upload it
in the region from here and submit it,
friends, you may have
some doubt here as to what question
answer will be asked in the interview, for that I have already made a call,
its link is
given in the description below, you can check out the call there, so
as soon as you submit here, the call will come to
you within 1 week from here
and
you can go there and give the interview or you can come here after giving the interview on the phone call, so
for now friends, if you like the video so much then like,
share and subscribe,
thank you.